{
    "subject": "resource/Kallar_(caste)",
    "predicate": "property/languages",
    "object": "resource/Tamil_language",
    "human_readable": "Kallar (caste) speaks Tamil language.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.986664891242981,
            "question": "Is Tamil a language spoken by the Kallar caste?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9145660400390625,
            "question": "Besides Tamil, are there any other languages spoken by the Kallar caste?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8707008361816406,
            "question": "What language does the Kallar caste speak?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8691977858543396,
            "question": "Are there any cultural implications associated with speaking Tamil for the Kallar caste?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7968302369117737,
            "question": "Which caste is associated with the Tamil language?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7837451100349426,
            "question": "Can you name a caste that speaks Tamil?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6826475858688354,
            "question": "What is the native language of the Kallar caste?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5874891877174377,
            "question": "To which linguistic group does the Kallar caste belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5759758353233337,
            "question": "How does language contribute to the identity of the Kallar caste?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4595644474029541,
            "question": "What is the primary language used within the Kallar community?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Kallar (caste) speaks Tamil language.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5786_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How does language contribute to the identity of the Kallar caste?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5786_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To which linguistic group does the Kallar caste belong?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5786_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the native language of the Kallar caste?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5786_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5786_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5786_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5786_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5786_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5786_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5786_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5786_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5786_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5786_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5786_58.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON response:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. The documents mention that \"Kallars are found largely in Thanjavur, Trichy, Pudukkottai, Theni Madurai, Dindigul, Sivagangai, Karur, kanchipuram, and Ramanathapuram districts of Tamil Nadu.\" and also state that \"They speak Tamil\". This indicates that the Kallar caste speaks the Tamil language."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents indicate that the Kallar caste is predominantly found in Tamil Nadu and they speak Tamil, which supports the statement that Kallar (caste) speaks Tamil language."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}